rusclothing.com 2011-11-25

# Privacy Policy - RusClothing.com

| **Customers comments**  
---  
_Dear Friends: Last week I decided I wanted to watch some of the lunar eclipse.I knew it was cold out and so I put on my beautiful brown Valenkis that go almost to my knees. The temperature was cold, -11F, and I decided to stay out only until I started to get uncomfortable. I watched a lot of the eclipse and thoroughly enjoyed my time outside, being very still, and very cozy. My fingers started to get chilly and my cheeks were cold, although my bare toes in my warm boots were just beginning to cool off. Imagine my surprise when I discovered that I'd been out in that sub-zero weather for almost an hour! I LOVE your boots!!!!! Thanks,_  
 ** _Pam, US_**  
more...  

[  
](http://www.twitter.com/rusclothing/)   
All major cards and  
PayPal payments with  

[  
Secure Site](http://www.comodogroup.com/)  

|    
[Home](http://www.rusclothing.com/)Privacy Policy   

| 

  * **Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available via our bottom menu posted at each end every page of the RusClothing.com website. 

  * **The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On our pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. To serve your orders properly we do need to collect some of your personal data. The types of personal information collected at this website are: 

Name, Address, Email address, Phone number. 

When checking out, you can also submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it to be sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's name, address and phone number. 

  * **The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you agree clearly mentioning that in our checkout form. 

  * **Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software that is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure online commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. 

  * **Cookie/Tracking Technology**

Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. 

Cookies we use at RusClothing.com website are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our system to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart during your visit as well as between visits.  
We may also use third party tracking technologies to better understand our visitors' behavior and needs. The third party counters may also set cookies to your hard drive, nevertheless NO personal information can be collected by these tracking technologies. 

  * **How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us using the information posted at our contact page. 

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted. 

|   
  
---|---
